

PROFILE

I am a goal-driven and ambitious sales professional with a background in ecommerce and experience as a meeting booker in the solar energy industry. I thrive in fast-paced environments, quickly adapt to new challenges, and have a strong ability to build relationships that drive business success.

My proactive mindset and eagerness to learn allow me to continuously develop and deliver results.

CONTACT

PHONE:

(+46)70 03 17 471

EMAIL:

aptsiauri20@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

Zaza Aptsiauri

COMPETENCIES

- Ambition
- Leadership
- Sales
- Stress management
- E-commers
- Creativity

ZAZA APTSIAURI

SALES REPRESENTATIVE

EDUCATION

Umeå University - Sports Science and Coaching Programme 2021-2024

Studies included sports psychology, focusing on the principles that contribute to effective leadership. Main studies were about the combination of strategic decision-making, emotional intelligence, and the ability to inspire and motivate others.

Swedish Armed Forces Norrbottens regemente I19 Boden 2020-2021

Military basic training as an infantry soldier and part-time plutoon leader.

Sandbackaskolan Gymnasium

2017-2020

High School Diploma in Business and Economics

WORK EXPERIENCE

SESOL - Sales Development Representative

Mar 2024 - Dec 2024

My role as an SDR was highly goal driven and involved mainly cold calling private property owners, booking meetings regarding counseling solar cells.

TS-Relations - Sales Development Representative

Dec 2024 - present

My role as an SDR was highly goal driven and involved mainly cold calling private property owners, booking meetings regarding counseling solar cells.

REFERENCE

Vicky Karazeimbeki

SESOL / Team Leader

Phone: (+46)761756966

Email: Karazeimbeki@gmail.com